hey I'm Chris I work at Twitter yeah in
嘿，我是克里斯，我在Twitter工作，是的
the VM team so Twitter has its own VM
VM团队，因此Twitter拥有自己的VM
team and if you tweet about this talk it
团队，如果您在此发表推文，
would be nice if you had that hashtag to
如果您有该标签，那将很好
give a little off to our team and so the
给我们的团队一些帮助，所以
talk what's the goal of this talk I'll
讲这个演讲的目的是什么
basically show you what we did at
基本上告诉你我们在做什么
Twitter with growl and and what the
Twitter与咆哮和什么
outcome was and and the goal for us was
结果是，而我们的目标是
always to save money right because
总是为了省钱，因为
Twitter is a big service lots of machine
Twitter是很多机器的重要服务
service and if you can shave off a bunch
服务，如果你能剃光一堆
of CPU time you will save a lot of money
CPU时间，您将节省很多钱
right so I guess everyone knows what
对，所以我想每个人都知道
Twitter is it's just you know to recap
Twitter是只有您知道
it's a huge distributed system we have
这是一个庞大的分布式系统
many many services I don't even know how
我什至不知道很多服务
many but there are some main services
很多，但有一些主要服务
like the tweet service right that reads
就像读的推特服务权利
and writes tweets and and they use a
并写推文，他们使用
service that shows you data off the
向您显示数据的服务
profiles and stuff like that and the
个人资料和类似的东西，以及
time line service which you know
你知道的时间线服务
provides you the time line on your
为您提供时间表
client app social graph you know all
您知道所有的客户端应用社交图
that stuff these are important services
这些东西是重要的服务
and and we run many instances of them so
并且我们运行它们的许多实例
we have many TV aims for service as I
我们有很多电视服务目标
just said especially the main ones
只是说了主要的
thousands of instances of one service
一项服务的数千个实例
and we have thousands of machines
我们有数千台机器
running thousands of gvm so we you know
运行数千个gvm，所以我们知道
all of every time a little bit of saving
每次都节省一点点
you can have multiplies thousand fold
你可以成千上万倍
right so and then on top of it we have
是的，然后最重要的是
multiple data centers who you know it's
您知道的多个数据中心
a big system right we also do open
一个大系统，我们也确实开放
source we use a lot of open source and
来源，我们使用了大量的开源资源，
there it there is this this link we have
那里有这个我们有的链接
lots of open source projects and github
很多开源项目和github
so when we thought about trying Raleigh
所以当我们考虑尝试罗利时
was a good fit because it's an open
很合适，因为它是开放的
source project you know you go and get
您知道您去得到的源项目
help you download it you try it out you
帮助您下载它，尝试一下
see how it works so that's a good fit
看看它是如何工作的，所以很合适
for us and it's also easy for us to
对我们来说，对我们来说也很容易
contribute back which we actually do so
贡献我们实际所做的
we have our own JDK built which is based
我们有自己的基于
on open JDK 8 you basically what we did
在开放的JDK 8上，您基本上做了什么
is so there is 243 that's the JVM CI
所以有243个是JVM CI
which we back ported from 9 to 8 into
我们从9移植到8
our JDK and then we have Grall in there
我们的JDK，然后在其中有Grall
and then we have something called
然后我们有一个叫做
contrail which is a chi of our
转换轨迹是我们的志气
replacement type of thing and and we
事物的替代类型，并且我们
have a bunch of CMS improvements so this
有很多CMS改进，所以这
is the JDK we're using and this this JDK
是我们正在使用的JDK，这个JDK
runs all of our services so why growling
运行我们所有的服务，为什么要咆哮
general is C - I didn't know how many
一般是C-我不知道有多少
people in this room know C - and not a
这个房间里的人知道C-而不是
lot of you know the source code of C -
你们很多人都知道C的源代码-
but it's really old and very complex and
但是它确实很老很复杂
getting ramped up on C - takes years
逐渐增加C语言-花费数年
right so it's it's very hard to hire
对，所以很难雇用
people very hard to train them and
人们很难训练他们，
sometimes they don't even stay long
有时他们甚至不留多久
enough to get to a point where they're
足以达到他们所处的位置
actually really useful and do the stuff
实际上非常有用，可以做一些事情
so that's where that's why in situ there
所以这就是为什么在那里原地
were no major optimizations in the last
过去没有重大优化
couple of years right there were there
几年就在那里
were small improvements especially
是小的改进，尤其是
intrinsic improvements until did a lot
内在的改进，直到做了很多
of work there but there was no major oh
那里的工作，但是没有专业哦
we redid the whole inlining or we
我们重做整个内联，否则我们
reimplemented it's capable nothing like
重新实现它无所不能
that happened right so and in my own
那是正确的，我自己
opinion it reached its end of life oh
认为它已经寿终正寝了哦
alright a couple of years ago so and
好吧，几年前
again probably in my opinion I think
再次可能在我看来，我认为
that broad is much easier to understand
这么广泛更容易理解
it has a modular design you have
它具有模块化设计
dependencies between the modules and the
模块与
build system takes care that you're not
构建系统会确保您不会
breaking these dependencies and you're
打破这些依赖关系，你
not introducing circular dependencies
不引入循环依赖
things
东西
that their modules that are
他们的模块是
platform-independent
平台无关
they can't depend on platform they
他们不能依赖平台
depend on module stuff like that so it
取决于这样的模块的东西，所以它
it has a really nice design and very
它的设计非常好，非常
important this that the inlining is much
重要的是内联非常重要
better and be escaped analysis - that's
更好并且可以逃脱的分析-那就是
where we mostly which you will see later
我们大部分会在后面看到
where that's where we gain so when we
那就是我们获得的地方，所以当我们
when I joined Twitter little more than a
当我加入Twitter时，
year ago the first thing was okay let's
一年前第一件事是好的，让我们
bring this over to our Twitter jdk and
把它带到我们的Twitter jdk，
see if it works right you know start up
看看它是否正确，你知道启动
a service and see if it works there were
服务，看看它是否有效
a few bugs I'll highlight a few of them
一些错误，我将重点介绍其中一些
there would there weren't you know it
那会不会你不知道
this is basically almost the whole list
这基本上是整个列表
- there was not a hundred bugs and I'm
-没有一百个错误，我是
showing you that the three most
向您展示三个最
important ones this is more or less what
重要的，这或多或少是什么
we found so it was this reoccurring
我们发现这就是这种情况
thing that on stack replacement
更换堆栈的东西
compilations didn't work because crawl
编译无效，因为抓取
didn't support or Czar's with locks with
不支持或沙皇与锁
synchronizations
同步化
so and we've up the bug for it the
因此，我们为此解决了错误
exception some things looked something
有些东西看起来很奇怪
like this right and then we discussed
像这样的权利，然后我们讨论了
this a little bit I discussed it with
这一点我与
Tom Rodriguez and we decided at that
汤姆·罗德里格斯（Tom Rodriguez），我们决定了这一点
time that was almost a year ago we just
差不多一年前的时间
say it's not really a big issue because
说这不是什么大问题，因为
basically grogg will fail a bunch of
基本上grogg会使一堆失败
times and then it will say okay I can
次，然后它会说可以
compile this one and see one will take
编译这个，然后看一个
care of it
照顾它
and and there were not you know
而且你不知道
important methods for us so we didn't
对我们来说很重要的方法，所以我们没有
care too much so but at some point
太在乎了，但是在某些时候
someone actually fixed it down there and
有人实际上将其固定在那里
since then it works so basically 128 is
从那以后它就可以正常工作了128
close but not really because when I
亲密，但不是真的，因为当我
tried to verify that it's actually
试图验证它实际上是
working there were a bunch of other ones
工作还有很多其他的
popping up like this
像这样弹出
no on secretase Monteux generated and
没有关于分泌酶Monteux的产生，
then there's this other one without or
然后有另一个没有或
is our entry loop I think that means I
是我们的进入循环，我认为这意味着我
can't
不能
so tom was asking for a bunch of graphs
所以汤姆要一堆图
and then for the first two ones I think
然后我认为前两个
yeah he he found out that there's a tiny
是的，他发现有一个微小的
little piece of code in situ that
原地的一小段代码
basically makes sure if you're accessing
基本上可以确保您是否正在访问
a static final field in a constructor
构造函数中的静态final字段
that you can actually do it because
您实际上可以做到，因为
otherwise if you can't you would compile
否则，如果不能编译
code that would be optimized as soon as
尽快进行优化的代码
you executed it so there wouldn't be a
您执行了它，所以不会有
point there would not be a point of
点不会有一点
doing it so that was just a timed up
这样做只是时间到了
that's the c2 equivalent method that
这就是c2的等效方法
does that right and so better to check
这样做正确，所以最好检查一下
now then did the optimized as soon as we
现在我们尽快进行优化
executed you know of course so that one
处决你当然知道，所以一个
was very easy to fix right it was only
修复起来非常容易，只是
like one file changed at basically a
就像一个文件基本上改变了
chava version of that method and do that
该方法的chava版本并执行该操作
and everything was good and we had this
一切都很好，我们有这个
bug that I only saw it with long-running
我只能长时间运行才看到的错误
processes and I was super annoying
程序，我很烦
because I thought oh my god if that's
因为我以为我的天哪
you know one of these compiler bugs that
您知道这些编译器错误之一
you that you'll find after days and you
你会在几天后找到你
don't even know where it's coming from
甚至不知道它来自哪里
so I would I dug around a little bit and
所以我会挖一点
then I found out that we're using it an
然后我发现我们正在使用它
agent called hipster and what it does it
代理人称为赶时髦的人，它是做什么的
it does some heat profiling and that
它进行一些热分析，并且
means it has to instrument the bytecode
表示必须检测字节码
and that changes some byte code of
并更改了一些字节码
especially allocation sites Graz written
特别是分配网站格拉茨写的
in Java so there's a kind of this you
在Java中，有一种您
know meta-circular bootstrapping problem
知道亚圆引导问题
so it turned out that it was it was an
所以事实证明那是
issue with something called byte code
问题叫做字节码
snippets it's something very special in
片段是非常特殊的
ground it's not a regular Java code type
它不是常规的Java代码类型
of thing that you compile down with Java
Java编译下来的东西
C and then you just run it it's treated
C然后运行它就可以了
specially by graph it's something like
特别是通过图它就像
an intrinsically put it this way so and
本质上这样说
that was an issue because suddenly the
这是一个问题，因为突然之间
byte code was changed for that snip
该代码段的字节码已更改
and that broke it so this one was closed
那把它弄坏了，所以这个被关闭了
with a rod a big change right but it
用杆很大的改变吧，但是
works now so that was good and we had
现在可以正常工作了，我们有
this one the service started up fine and
这项服务启动正常，
suddenly the log would grow and grow and
突然，日志会越来越大，
I thought what's going on right and it
我以为发生了什么事
was throwing exceptions like crazy all
都在疯狂地抛出异常
the time and I didn't know where it was
时间，我不知道它在哪里
coming from right and and this was going
从右边来，这正在
on for at least a couple of weeks and I
至少持续几个星期，我
didn't know really where to start to
真的不知道从哪里开始
look where it's failing I was digging
看看我在哪里挖
around in core library code and seeing
在核心库代码中看到
where the exception was coming from and
异常来自何处
so on and then at one point you know
如此反复，然后在某一时刻，你知道
sometimes to help you have to put things
有时要帮助你放东西
on the side and do something else and so
一边做其他事情等等
that's what I did and then I was I was
那就是我所做的，那时我就是
running nettie tests at the test suite
在测试套件上运行nettie测试
and I found out that the buffer one
我发现缓冲区之一
failed and the reason for that is there
失败了，原因在那里
is like an optimization in most
在大多数情况下就像一个优化
compilers that when you do a reverse buy
编译器，当您进行反向购买时
could that it just you know swapped it
你知道可以交换吗
around with one machine instruction that
带着一条机器指令
one was broken right it didn't swap the
一个被打破了，它没有交换
bytes which is surprising because it
字节，这是令人惊讶的，因为它
should fail all the time right but it
应该一直失败，但是
did not so we fixed that that was really
并非如此，我们确定那是真的
easy five change files so that was
简单的五个更改文件，因此
alright and that was really it these
好吧，真的就是这些
were all the bugs we found and since
是我们发现的所有错误，并且
then we basically run and growl in all
然后我们基本上跑起来
of our services at least the ones we run
我们的服务，至少是我们提供的服务
we don't run all of them on grout but
我们不是全部用灌浆
the ones we do run fine
我们做的很好
we started contributing back a little
我们开始回馈一点
bit this is still work-in-progress
有点，这仍在进行中
so one thing I started doing is because
所以我开始做的一件事是因为
you know when I did the slides 9 wasn't
你知道我什么时候幻灯片9不是
out yet but now it is so it would be
出来，但现在是这样
good if we had that 9 has something
好的，如果我们有那9有东西
called compact compact strings and the
称为紧凑型紧凑型琴弦，
implementation is a lot of intrinsic
实现是很多内在的
code unfortunately because C 2
代码很不幸，因为C 2
especially and also C 1 and to some
特别是C 1和某些
degree couldn't handle on safe
学位无法保证安全
implementations and in a good way so he
实施并以一种很好的方式，所以他
couldn't if you would implement the
如果您要实施
the methods with unsafe you could not
不安全的方法
get the same performance if you were
如果您曾经
right an intrinsic for it that was
对它来说是内在的
unfortunate but that's the way it is so
不幸的是，事实就是这样
they're a bunch of methods in in situ
他们是一堆就地方法
that are hand optimized SSE AVX avx-512
手动优化的SSE AVX avx-512
so we need to port this over to grab to
所以我们需要将其移植到
get the same performance so that I
获得相同的性能，以便我
started doing that I started with the
开始做，我从
first one so far it's the which one is
到目前为止，第一个是
it
它
oh yeah the string compare to method and
哦是的字符串比较方法和
you can see the that was yeah with still
你可以看到那仍然是
the case because I haven't pushed it yet
案件，因为我还没有推
so if you download ah you get like these
所以如果你下载啊，你会得到这些
scores and then at the bottom you see
得分，然后在底部看到
especially you know the third line with
特别是你知道第三行
the biggest size you see it's much
您看到的最大尺寸
faster and that's exactly what do you
更快，那正是你的目的
get with C do so I just showed this and
和C一起做，所以我刚刚展示了这个
tell you C 2 is the same performance so
告诉你C 2是一样的表现
we need to part all these as I said I'm
我需要分开所有这些
still working on this one I need to add
仍在为此工作，我需要添加
a test case of course and we might want
当然是一个测试用例，我们可能想要
to make it work with JDK two so we'll
使它与JDK两个一起工作，所以我们将
see and then they're like three four ish
看，然后他们就像三四
more of them but they're up there
他们更多，但他们在那里
smaller well we'll get there so numbers
较小的井，我们会到达那里，所以数字
I think that's the interesting part I
我认为那是我有趣的部分
chose the treat service which is one of
选择了请客之一
our bigger ones not the biggest service
我们更大的不是最大的服务
but it's it's like the first one I've
但这就像我第一个
tried so I was just using that one it
尝试过，所以我只是用那个
doesn't really matter it's it's a
并不重要，这是一个
finagle thrift service so finagle is an
finagle节俭服务，所以finagle是一个
open source project that you can
您可以的开源项目
download and check it out
下载并签出
I couldn't tell you exactly what it is
我无法确切地告诉你这是什么
because I don't really know but it's
因为我真的不知道，但是
some HTTP you know save me a thrift
您知道的一些HTTP可以节省我很多钱
request and I'll give you something back
请求，我会给你一些东西
type of thing so this one runs 100% on
事物的类型，因此这100％
Gras in production like all the
像所有
instances we have run on grog today
我们今天在熟料上跑的实例
including a bunch of other services not
包括一堆其他服务
limited to DS but including also they
仅限于DS，但也包括它们
use the servers into social craft
使用服务器参与社交活动
service or pretty much everything you do
服务或您所做的几乎所有事情
on the web or on your
在网络上还是在您的
Twitter client runs through brawl
Twitter客户端通过斗殴运行
generated code today and I think it
今天生成的代码，我认为
works fine right does it so it it's like
可以正常工作，就像
testing it is a little tricky especially
测试它特别棘手
in the data center you know first you
在数据中心，您首先了解
have different types of machines
有不同类型的机器
different hardware then you have
不同的硬件，那么你有
obviously not just one process running
显然，不仅有一个进程在运行
on the machine so you have very noisy
在机器上，所以你很吵
neighbors and things like that so the
邻居和类似的事情，所以
test setup I have is is one dedicated
我的测试设置是专用的
machine for one instance exact same
一台机器完全一样
hardware I run with JVM CI syrup on 30
我在30上使用JVM CI糖浆运行的硬件
and Gras VM 0.22 which is slightly old
和Gras VM 0.22，这有点旧
now I think we are it's your 30 years
现在我想这是你的30年
something like this I can't remember but
这样的事情我不记得了
it's still about the same performance we
它仍然与我们的性能差不多
we do it you know pretty standard tiered
我们做到了，您知道非常标准的分层
setup so we we compile with c1 and then
设置，所以我们用c1进行编译，然后
we compile with with growl as as the
我们用咆哮作为
top-level compiler talk to your compiler
顶级编译器与您的编译器对话
and to it's it's pretty much like what
而且就好像是什么
do you have today when you download
你今天有下载吗
Oracle or OpenJDK we just replace we
甲骨文或OpenJDK，我们只是取代我们
swap out CT with well that's all there
用那里的所有东西换掉CT
is something I'm not going into details
这是我不详述的事情
here but since Grodd is written in Java
在这里，但是因为Grodd是用Java编写的
you when you start compiling your
当您开始编译您的
application and you start compiling your
应用程序，然后开始编译您的
first hot methods with the top tier
顶级的第一个热门方法
withdrawal itself crawl will execute as
提款本身爬网将执行为
Java code and then it will compile
Java代码，然后将其编译
itself which is you know that can't take
本身就是你知道不能接受
up some time of your startup you can do
可以花一些时间来启动
something called Agora bootstrap with a
叫做Agora bootstrap的东西
command-line option that usually take
通常需要的命令行选项
depending on your machine and how many
取决于您的机器和数量
threads you're using but that takes
您正在使用的线程，但这需要
between you know let's say fifteen or
您知道我们之间是十五岁还是
thirty seconds something like this right
三十秒钟左右
so if you just let it go you know let it
所以如果你随它去就知道
run it kind of eats twenty seconds into
跑进去吃了二十秒钟
your application startup you just read
您刚刚阅读的应用程序启动
out across your first minute or
在您的第一分钟内
something
某事
but for us it really doesn't matter
但是对我们来说真的没关系
because we start up the services they
因为我们启动了他们的服务
warm up themselves anyway they have to
无论如何都要热身
talk to a bunch of neighbors to set up
与一群邻居交谈建立
all the you know routes and connections
所有你知道的路线和联系
and whatnot so it was never it no it's
什么都没有，所以从来没有，不是
not true unlike it was once an issue
不像以前那样是一个问题
because there is some kind of a watchdog
因为有某种看门狗
timeout that makes sure that the service
超时，以确保该服务
actually came up and and they had a tiny
实际上出现了，他们有一个很小的
little bit of margin then we just pushed
一点利润然后我们就推
it over the edge but we increased it by
它超过边缘，但我们增加了
a few seconds and everything was cool so
几秒钟，一切都很酷，所以
if that's an issue for you for us it
如果这对您来说对我们来说是一个问题
isn't at this point but in JDK 9 you can
目前还没有，但是在JDK 9中，您可以
you can t compile ghrelin and all this
你可以编译ghrelin和所有这些
goes away but since we're running on 8
消失了，但是因为我们在8跑
we can't do that so this is this is one
我们不能这样做，所以这是一个
day of requests per second so this I'm
每秒请求的天数，所以我
just showing this slide so that you can
只显示这张幻灯片，以便您可以
trust me that all of them get the exact
相信我，他们所有人都能得到准确的
same requests that's very important
同样的要求非常重要
because if a tweet you know forget it
因为如果您知道一条推文，那就算了
three requests and and the tweet has one
三个请求，并且该推文有一个
character or 140 characters - 80 to 80
字符或140个字符-80至80
characters that's a big difference in
字符差异很大
how much memory you have to allocate
您必须分配多少内存
right so all of them get the exact same
对，所以他们所有人都完全一样
requests for the same tweet IDs and so
请求相同的推特ID等
on so dedicated machines save requests I
在专用机器上保存请求
had some 24 hours oh yeah and I can't
有24小时哦，是的，我不能
you will notice there is no y-axis
您会注意到没有y轴
because I can't tell you the exact
因为我不能告诉你确切的
numbers obviously but we'll get to some
明显的数字，但我们会讲一些
relative numbers later and then so this
相对数字，然后这样
particular service runs parallel GC and
特定服务运行并行GC，并且
this is c2 at the bottom you see the
这是底部的c2，您会看到
colors and the compilers right this is
颜色和编译器对，这是
c2 that's how many scavenge cycles we do
c2这就是我们执行的清除周期
and it's it's a moving average of 16
这是16的移动平均线
minutes because otherwise it's neither
分钟，因为否则
jumping up and down but it gives you a
跳来跳去，但它给你一个
good idea right
好主意吧
this is grown so we're already saving
这已经长了，所以我们已经在保存
here quite a bit
这里相当多
I throw in JDK 9 as well just to show
我也投了JDK 9只是为了展示
you that it's roughly the same
你那差不多
I have to I didn't put that in the
我必须没有把它放在
slides but what do you get when you
幻灯片，但是当您得到什么
download open JDK 9 with Oracle JDK 9 is
下载带有Oracle JDK 9的打开JDK 9是
not the corral version that I'm using
不是我使用的畜栏版本
here basically I'm using because when
我基本上在这里使用，因为当
JDK 9 was prepared you know there's a
JDK 9已准备就绪，您知道其中有一个
there's a long time ramp down phases and
有很长时间的下降阶段
so on and so on
依此类推
I think the pro version that it actually
我认为它实际上是专业版
in JDK 9 is from December last year so
在JDK 9中是从去年12月开始的，所以
and then there were a bunch of
然后有一堆
improvements in the first couple months
前几个月的改善
of this year so when I've been using is
所以今年我一直在用的是
better than the one you would get when
比你会得到的更好
you download it today but you can go to
您今天就下载了，但是您可以转到
github go to Groth download that built
github转到内置的Groth下载
the module add a bunch of funky
该模块添加了一堆时髦
command-line arguments and you get the
命令行参数，您将获得
same thing this is really just to show
这真的只是为了展示同样的事情
that there's no difference between eight
八个之间没有区别
and nine and growl as you can see it's
和九，咆哮，正如你所看到的
the same so so we already saving there
一样，所以我们已经保存在那里
so if we don't have to this this means
因此，如果我们不必这样做，这意味着
two things right first of all we are
首先有两件事，我们是
saving the garbage collection time but
节省垃圾收集时间，但是
the the more important thing here is
更重要的是
that since we're actually not producing
因为我们实际上没有生产
as much garbage we are producing much
我们生产了多少垃圾
better code and escape analysis works
更好的代码和转义分析工作
better this is what we really want right
更好的是这是我们真正想要的
so we get like when when the loads high
所以我们得到的时候就像负载很高
we get 2.7 percent less scavenge cycles
我们的清理周期减少了2.7％
and 2.5 at the bottom let's say 2.5 old
底部是2.5，比方说2.5
chin is something that this question I
下巴是这个问题，我
get them a lot on I think Jim it just
让他们受益匪浅，我想吉姆
does that and it also does which I've we
做到了，我也做到了
don't have really good metrics to show
没有非常好的指标可显示
that but I'm just telling you and you
那只是我告诉你和你
have to believe me but it's it's this
必须相信我，但就是这样
it's the same for metadata right you
对元数据来说也是一样的
load a bunch of classes in it has a
加载一堆类中有一个
bunch of methods you have to allocate
一堆你必须分配的方法
some metadata but it's not people freak
一些元数据，但不是让人发狂
out right they say wait next slide it's
正确，他们说等待下一张幻灯片是
roughly 40 40 megabytes but people
大约40 40兆字节，但人
freaked out because they think all this
吓坏了，因为他们认为这一切
will grow right no that's it right it's
会长大，不，是这样，是
40 it will never change if the old chin
40如果老下巴永远不会改变
is 200 Meg's of will be 40 of the old
是200兆，将是40兆
chin is 10 gigs it will be 40 right
下巴是10演出，将是40
there's no difference
没有区别
and and growl doesn't suddenly grow
而且咆哮不会突然增长
inside so anything it just has its its
里面什么都只有它
state and that's it so this is the
状态，就是这样，这就是
important one right this is what the
重要的一项权利是
whole talks about CP q10 let's see to
关于CP q10的整个话题，让我们来看看
this crawl there's a situ taken now
这个爬行现在有一个原地
which is surprising you know what can
令人惊讶的是，您知道可以
happen is that that especially when you
发生的是，特别是当你
run teared that in laning decisions can
奔跑着，在对线的决定中可以
be different from run to run so I think
每次跑都不同，所以我认为
that's that I don't think that c2 is
那就是我不认为c2是
actually better in GT k9 I think it just
实际上在GT k9中更好，我认为
made slightly smarter decisions on that
对此做出了更明智的决定
instance - in line then on the one
实例-在一行上然后
before and that's Carl cheetah k9 same
之前和那是卡尔·猎豹k9一样
and now I can show you why X is right -
现在我可以告诉你为什么X是正确的-
ratio so this is it and we're saving 11%
就是这样，我们节省了11％
of CPU this is huge I mean I don't know
CPU的数量巨大，我的意思是我不知道
how many compiler engineers are in this
有多少个编译器工程师
room but if you ever worked on a
房间，但如果您曾经在
compiler and try to make something
编译器并尝试做点什么
better and faster you you know you you
更快更好地了解你
you crawl around down there and the one
你在那儿爬来爬去
percent range and you're it's super
百分比范围，你就是超级
happy if it's - right 11 is ridiculous
如果很高兴-正确的11是荒谬的
so I I never expected that right when I
所以我从没想到我会这样
when I joined Twitter I pitched this
当我加入Twitter时，我提出了这个建议
idea that oh look there's a yes compiler
哦，看起来有一个可以编译的想法
it's an Oracle labs research project no
这是一个Oracle实验室研究项目，否
one has ever used it in production
一个人曾经在生产中使用过它
before but I think it would help us in
以前，但我认为这会帮助我们
America let's try it as a one
美国让我们一起尝试
super-stoked there worked out otherwise
超级累了，否则就解决了
that would be don't have a job right now
那将是现在没有工作
so how much
那么多少
I can't tell you obviously but we can't
我显然不能告诉你，但我们不能
you know just make up some random
你知道只是随机组成
numbers and get at least get a feel for
数字，至少可以体会到
it right so let's assume you have a
没错，所以假设您有一个
company and and you're hosting your
公司，而您正在托管您的
stuff in the cloud right so I was I was
在云中的东西，所以我当时
typing in cloud hosting service prices
输入云托管服务价格
probably into Google and a bunch of them
可能进入了Google及其他人
popped up they all have different prices
弹出，他们都有不同的价格
and different ways of to calculate them
以及计算它们的不同方法
and show it to you so basically I did
并展示给你，基本上我做了
the calculation for you it's like from
您的计算就像
$170 per year per pair one CPU core - no
每年每对$ 170，一个CPU内核-否
wait the other way around 72 to 210 so
等到72到210左右
choose your cloud provider vice Lee it's
选择您的云提供商副李，这是
makes a big difference
有很大的不同
so it's you know let's say the average
所以说平均数
is 100 $27 per CPU per year so then of
是每个CPU每年100 $ 27，因此
obviously how many quarts do you have as
显然你有多少夸脱
I said you know earlier about Twitter we
我说过您较早了解Twitter
have lots you you might not but in fact
有很多你可能没有，但实际上
it doesn't really matter because oh wait
没关系，因为哦，等等
no I didn't want to go there because the
不，我不想去那里，因为
size of the company also has to do with
公司的规模也与
your revenue in a way right so and if
您的收入是否正确，如果
you have two servers and you have to
你有两个服务器，你必须
spin okay - is my finale enough but say
好吧-我的结局够了，但说
you have 10 and you have to spend $2,000
您有10个，您必须花费$ 2,000
a year for them if you could save 10%
如果他们可以节省10％，一年
$200 you would be happy right if it's in
200美元，如果它在你会很高兴
the millions yeah it's a lot of money
数以百万计的是很多钱
for us but for the company it's still
对我们而言，但对公司而言，仍然
only 10 percent right so it doesn't
只有百分之十的权利，所以它不是
really matter but you know just just to
真的很重要，但是你知道
get a feel for how big things can be and
感受事物有多大，
to be honest I didn't even know how big
老实说我什至不知道有多大
twitter is but so there was an article
推特是，但有一篇文章
this was one I found right you can
我发现这是你可以的
google it maybe there's even an article
谷歌，也许甚至有一篇文章
about Twitter how many servers we have I
关于Twitter，我们有多少台服务器
don't know
不知道
that's from 2014 so it's already three
那是从2014年开始的，所以已经是三个
years old they're talking about two
岁，他们在谈论两个
million servers right they say something
一百万台服务器，他们说了些什么
from data centers fifty to eighty
从数据中心五十到八十
thousand servers and
千台服务器和
I don't know 24 cores so a lot right
我不知道24核那么多
your company's definitely smaller than
您的公司肯定比
Google I would assume so I'm gonna pick
Google，我认为是，所以我会选择
a random though of 10,000 servers a I
随机，但有10,000台服务器
think that's reasonable
认为这是合理的
each is usually 24 cores or you multiply
每个通常是24核，或者您乘以
that out three million dollars you have
那三百万美元
to pay just to run your whatever you
付钱只是为了经营自己的东西
have right you can save to 11 percent of
有权利，您可以节省11％
that
那
that's more than a salary here in the
这比这里的薪水还多
Bay Area so you know you can hire one
湾区，所以您知道您可以租一个
more guy so can we save even more
更多的人，所以我们可以节省更多
potentially I was just you know I I
可能我只是你知道
spent one afternoon really toying around
花了一个下午真的在玩弄
Groth has a bunch of in landing
格罗斯（Groth）有很多着陆点
parameters as c2 does so I was touring
参数，就像c2一样，所以我正在巡回演出
around and again my best side the
到处都是我最好的一面
request and I did an experiment which
要求，我做了一个实验
you know it's just another instance of
你知道这只是
my of my dedicated cluster and so this
我的专用集群，所以这
is what we've seen before and this is my
是我们以前见过的，这是我的
experiment so we get less scavenge
实验，这样我们就可以减少清理工作
cycles again and about 1.5 percent less
再次循环，减少约1.5％
which is quite a bit and CPU time it
这是相当多的时间和CPU时间
amounts to this a little bit and on the
等于这一点，在
ratio we're not a 2 percent and that
比率我们不是2％，那
that was only like four hours of really
真的只有四个小时
just randomly picking in lining numbers
只是随机选择衬里号码
right so I think that there is a lot
对，所以我认为有很多
more you can get you might not be able
更多，您可以获得，您可能无法
to get it with at least that's what
至少要得到它
that's my current thinking I wanted to
这是我目前的想法
mention here but I think I forgot I just
在这里提到，但我想我忘了我只是
mentioned now
现在提到
people on my team on the Twitter VN team
Twitter VN团队中我团队中的人
they're actually working on if get the
他们实际上正在努力，如果得到
gift gave presentations and I wanted to
礼物做了演讲，我想
link it about something called auto-tune
将其链接到称为自动调谐的内容
that does you can tell the machine
那你可以告诉机器
learning thing to you know try different
要学习的东西，尝试不同
cbn parameters and tell you which one's
cbn参数并告诉您哪个
the best so that that's what we want to
最好的，这就是我们想要的
try you know tell it Oh
尝试告诉你哦
try these in learning parents from A to
尝试这些方法来学习从A到
B and you know play around with the
B，你知道玩
machine learning a little bit and then
机器学习一点，然后
giving me back what's the best that's
还给我什么是最好的
what we want to do but at this point I
我们想做什么，但在这一点上，我
have a feeling that the inlining policy
觉得内联政策
that's the default in Gras is not really
那不是Gras的默认值
the right one for it I think we have to
正确的选择，我认为我们必须
possibly write our own to get to better
可能写我们自己来变得更好
numbers so that's probably important to
数字，这可能对
you it's it's to a degree important for
你在某种程度上很重要
us too but at this point you know we are
我们也是，但在这一点上，你知道我们是
happy right we have a compiler that
很高兴，我们有一个编译器
works we have our own VM team we have a
我们有自己的VM团队，我们有一个
bunch of people who can work on problems
一群可以解决问题的人
if they come up I think all of you have
如果他们出现了，我想你们所有人都有
your own VM team so you might be
您自己的VM团队，因此您可能会
interested in official support for that
对官方支持感兴趣
so yeah we'll see you know JD canine has
是的，我们会看到你知道JD犬有
Gras because the ante solution in JDK 9
Gras因为JDK 9中的ante解决方案
actually uses Gras so and what's not
实际使用Gras而不是
announced by Oracle is that you can
甲骨文宣布，您可以
actually use that version of growl
实际使用那个咆哮声
that's in the Cherokee you can actually
那实际上是在切诺基
use it as a chicken platter it's a it's
用它作为鸡肉拼盘
an experimental option that's why they
一个实验性的选择，这就是为什么他们
didn't announce it or or not even that
没有宣布，甚至没有宣布
so hey you can't use it but at this
所以嘿，你不能用它
point it's not supported
指出它不受支持
but so there was this email on the
但是，这封电子邮件上有
mailing list completely innocent looking
邮件列表看起来完全天真
right
对
it just says okay let's build cross we
只是说好吧，让我们建立交叉我们
crawled regardless of if you build it he
不管您是否建造它都爬行
or not but there's one important
是否有一个重要的
sentence in here let me zoom in on that
这里的句子让我放大
one that they would like to do growth as
他们想做的一种
an experiment chicken pate the next
实验鸡酱下一个
release which at the time when this was
释放当时是
sent Oracle didn't announced the new
发送甲骨文没有宣布新
release cadence so this sentence would
释放节奏，所以这句话会
mean Cheney content and I exactly sure
是切尼的意思，我很确定
what that means today if that means 18.3
如果今天意味着18.3，那么今天意味着什么
or not we'll see the the only thing I
不然我们会看到我唯一的
know is that the JDK 9 version that I
知道是我的JDK 9版本
would see the chorale version in JDK 9
会在JDK 9中看到合唱版本
that I was using was basically back
我使用的基本上回来了
ported all the cheetah quitan change
移植了所有猎豹的戒烟改变
sets from upstream I didn't I didn't
从上游出发我没有
want to put it myself I just took the
想要自己说，我只是拿了
change to the Europe like them they
像他们一样去欧洲
apply cleanly and and that was it so in
干净地涂抹，就是这样
the mainline of open JDK right now is
现在打开JDK的主线是
the growl version that I was using and
我正在使用的咆哮版本
that it might be 18.3 or 18.9 so you
可能是18.3或18.9，所以您
might have to wait a year but what I'm
可能要等一年，但是我
trying to say is I think we'll get
想说的是我想我们会得到
official support pretty soon so if you
官方支持很快，所以如果你
want to toy around with that do it today
想今天一起玩
we run it in production we don't have an
我们在生产中运行它，我们没有
issue there might be you know smaller
问题可能是您知道较小
bugs that you run into but there's a
您遇到的错误，但是有一个
community for it you file a bug and
为此，您提交了一个错误，并且
github and will be fixed right so do you
github，将被修复，所以你呢
want to save some money you can do it
想省些钱就可以做到
that way I'm not saying everyone will
这样我不是说每个人都会
get 10% right I'm not saying that but
得到10％的权利我不是说那
there's there's the possibility that you
有可能你
can and I think that wasn't my last
可以，我认为那不是我的最后一次
slide actually so
实际如此滑动
give it a try really this this is this
试试看，这真的是这个
isn't my my message I'm going to you
不是我的讯息我要去找你
know do a road show with that talk I
我知道我会跟那个路演
want people to know that it actually
希望人们知道它实际上
works um I don't know
我不知道
as Lee as far as I know we are the only
据我所知，李是我们唯一的
ones who actually use that in production
在生产中实际使用它的人
there might be companies out there
可能有公司在那里
somewhere that I don't know about right
我不知道的地方
smaller companies but I think at a
较小的公司，但我认为
bigger scale we are the only ones who
更大的规模是我们唯一的
are doing this and it works great for us
正在这样做，对我们很有用
and we are we want to move all of our
而且我们是我们想要移动我们所有的
services to grow I'm not exactly sure
服务增长我不确定
when that will happen but you know there
什么时候会发生，但你知道那里
will be the odd one out that won't work
将是一个奇怪的，将无法正常工作
or will run slower or who knows but but
或会慢一些，或者谁知道，但是
we want to get there because so far I
我们想到达那里，因为到目前为止
mean as I said earlier we have thousands
就像我之前说的，我们有成千上万
of servers I don't know how many so far
到目前为止我不知道有多少台服务器
we've converted maybe not even 20 right
我们已经转换了，甚至可能还不到20
we started with the big ones because
我们从大公司开始，因为
there you get the most savings but still
在那里您可以获得最多的节省，但仍然
the smaller ones add up so the amount of
较小的加起来，所以
dollars we're saving today per year will
我们每年节省的美元将
be double or triple once we're done
完成后变成两倍或三倍
that's the whole thing if you tweet
如果你发推特，那就是整件事
about it let my team know thank you
关于这一点，请让我的团队知道谢谢
[Applause]
[掌声]
question
题
if inlining depends on the cpu no no it
如果内联取决于cpu否否
really doesn't
真的不
I know we talked before to talk a little
我知道我们之前聊过一点
bit about it so I think I know what
一点点，所以我想我知道
you're aiming at so growl has support
你的目标是让咆哮声有支持
for some vector instruction sets it's
对于某些矢量指令集
not how should I say this well one thing
不是我该怎么说一件事
that's missing in growl at least in the
至少在咆哮中缺少
open-source version is that it's not
开源版本不是
doing vectorization at all which c2 has
c2具有的所有向量
for us it it didn't matter so far there
对我们来说，到目前为止没有关系
might be a service that I don't know of
可能是我不知道的服务
yet that will need it and then we have
但这将需要它，然后我们有了
to do something about it but today it
做一些事情，但今天
does not do vectorization but that
不进行矢量化，但是
doesn't mean that it's not using vector
并不意味着它没有使用向量
instructions for for other types of
其他类型的说明
things it's just not vectorizing Loops
事情不是矢量化循环
Oh
哦
well yeah it can in a way it usually
是的，它通常可以以某种方式
doesn't but you know in lining it's it's
不，但是你知道衬里是
just it's this walk on the edge between
只是这条路在
pushing it over the edge of the method
将其推到方法的边缘
becoming too big right because that your
变得太大了吧，因为
instruction cache is basically
指令缓存基本上是
influencing that so but I didn't really
因此，但我并没有真正
follow how the instruction caches are
遵循指令缓存的方式
today but they were all up about the
今天，但他们都为
same size right on me
我身上的尺码一样
right
对
I did not the reason why I did not is
我不是没有我的原因是
because it you know I basically the last
因为你知道我基本上是最后一个
year
年
besides you know preparing that JDK and
除了您知道准备JDK和
I'm putting the stuff over and including
我把东西放进去，包括
it in a chicken makes you know test it
把它放在鸡里会让你知道测试它
to make sure that it works fine I spend
为了确保它能正常工作，我花了
most of my time hand-holding service
我大部分时间都是手工服务
owners right it's like you go to a
业主，就好像您去了
server zona and he's responsible for the
服务器zona，他负责
thing to be up and you will get into
事情要起来，你会进入
trouble when Twitter's down but and then
麻烦，当Twitter关闭，然后
you go to them and say hey look I have
你去找他们说嘿，我有
to remember that no one ever used it
记住没有人使用过它
before you want to try it yeah so I
在你想尝试之前，是的，我
spend most of my time social engineering
花大部分时间进行社会工程
than actually engineering so no I did
比实际工程要多，所以我没有
not have time for that but it should be
没有时间，但是应该
done yet
做完了
right I I also don't fully know but I'm
对，我也不太了解，但我
pretty sure that most of the savings
可以肯定的是，大部分节省
we're seeing is is because we're just
我们看到的是因为我们只是
allocating less memory and add that also
分配更少的内存并添加
means you get tighter code right you
意味着您可以获得更严格的代码
don't have to you know call out to to
不必知道您要致电到
the runtime allocate the code and so on
运行时分配代码，依此类推
and so on so you can your code gets a
依此类推，这样您的代码就可以
little tighter one thing that I was
我当时有点紧
thinking about I should I shouldn't run
想着我不应该跑步
this experiment really turn off escape
这个实验真的关闭了逃生
analysis for both competitors and see if
分析两个竞争对手，看看是否
that changes anything there is I can I'm
改变了我所能拥有的一切
not sure if there's another talk about
不确定是否还有其他谈论
Enterprise crawl at JavaOne this year
企业今年在JavaOne上进行爬网
but it's basically Oracle labs as its
但基本上是Oracle实验室
it's a pure add-on to the open source
这是开源的纯附件
version and that one has as far as I
版本，据我所知
know vectorization support and it has
知道矢量化支持，它具有
better inlining as far as I know we've
据我所知，更好的内联
tried it I did not present the numbers
尝试过我没有提供数字
in this talk but I've done it before so
在这次演讲中，但我之前已经做过
I have previous talks somewhere that
我以前的演讲在某个地方
actually shown am was within the price
实际显示的价格在价格范围内
crawl as well and and they're impressive
爬行也很令人印象深刻
so the I just tried it last week
所以我上周刚尝试过
actually again because I wanted to see
其实又是因为我想看
where it stands today but I think it was
今天的位置，但我认为那是
like the 11% you saw Enterprise crawl I
就像您看到的11％的企业爬网一样
think was 22 and that also means that I
认为是22岁，这也意味着我
know that we still can get more
知道我们还能得到更多
so that $300,000 number you saw earlier
这样您之前看到的$ 300,000
is 600 now or can be right yeah it's
现在是600还是可以的，是的
it's not open source it's it's a
它不是开源的，这是一个
commercial product you have to pay for
您必须付费的商业产品
it but yeah well I'm it depends on the
但是，是的，我取决于
license you are getting from Oracle um
您从Oracle um获得的许可证
your negotiation skills are more
您的谈判技巧更多
important to you then I guess but yeah
那对你很重要，我想但是
if the money you were paying is less
如果您所付的钱少
than the money you're saving yeah go for
比省下的钱要多
it
它
against the workloads oh yes yeah that's
反对工作量哦，是的，那是
true
真正
that's a very good question and I can't
这是一个很好的问题，我不能
really answer that because Twitter is
真的回答，因为Twitter是
like 95% Scala and I don't know of any
像95％的Scala，我一无所知
service that's actually written 100% in
实际写成100％的服务
Java because most of our service is run
Java，因为我们的大多数服务都在运行
on finagle it's just the basic framework
在finagle上，这只是基本框架
that's written in Scala so you know I'm
那是用Scala写的，所以你知道我
not sure it it might not be as much so
不知道可能不会那么多
I'm really not a scholar expert but from
我真的不是学者专家，但来自
the rumors are here is that it allocates
谣言在这里是它分配
more temporary objects then Scala does
比Scala还要更多的临时对象
other than Java does so that would
除了Java之外，
explain why we are seeing you know less
解释为什么我们看到你了解得更少
scavenge cycles we allocate less memory
清理周期，我们分配更少的内存
because because all these temporary ones
因为因为所有这些临时的
day with better inlining that could just
内联更好的一天
scale replaced so I'm not sure it can
秤已更换，所以我不确定是否可以
probably not tan
可能不是棕褐色
but if you get 5 I mean it's still
但是如果你得到5，我的意思是
amazing
惊人
yeah I was bringing that up a bunch of
是的，我提起了一堆
times it's like all the other languages
就像其他所有语言一样
we use they're just not big enough we
我们用它们还不够大
use other languages for different things
使用其他语言处理不同的事情
but it's it's nothing's as big as
但它没有什么比它大
everything that runs on top of the of
一切都在
the JVM like Scala a little bit of Java
像Scala这样的JVM有点Java
so I I don't think so I was pitching the
所以我不这么认为
idea of you know we have sometimes we
你的想法知道我们有时
have these odd languages that run just
这些奇怪的语言只运行
this one service we probably acquired at
我们可能在
some point in time and it's this
某个时间点就是
outdated
过时的
who knows what Python version or whatnot
谁知道什么版本的Python
it would be good if if we could you know
如果我们能知道的话会很好
my great dad
我的曾父
to the JVM and then we could leverage
到JVM，然后我们可以利用
something like truffle yeah
像松露耶
yeah
是的
that's true so I left that out purposely
没错，所以我故意把它排除在外
because that's that's another Holt are
因为那是另一个霍尔特
talking about this so there there are
谈论这个所以有
two main issues with having a compiler
拥有编译器的两个主要问题
written in Java and one is the
用Java编写的，一个是
bootstrapping issue with which I briefly
我简要介绍的自举问题
touched and the other one is the
感动，另一个是
allocation on the Java heap problem the
Java堆分配问题
main issue with that one is when you are
一个人的主要问题是你什么时候
later in your run and your application
稍后在您的运行和应用程序中
is already fully up and using all of
已经完全使用了所有
your heap because everyone's tightly
你的堆，因为每个人都紧紧地
tuning the heaps of their application
调整应用程序的堆
just fits into the heap right that's
恰好适合堆
what everyone does if if you then
如果你那么每个人都会做什么
suddenly would get I don't know if
突然会得到我不知道是否
everyone knows what a deoptimization is
每个人都知道什么是去优化
but if you suddenly have to kick out one
但是如果你突然不得不踢出一个
of your compiled methods and recompile
编译方法并重新编译
it it could kick you over over the
它可能会把你踢过来
boundary and give you an out of memory
边界，让您记忆犹新
and the way it is today this out of
以及今天的方式
memory era could end up anywhere he
记忆时代可能会结束他的任何地方
could up if you're lucky in the compiler
如果您在编译器中很幸运，可以
but it usually won't you want to end up
但是通常你不想结束
in the application and the application
在应用程序和应用程序中
goes down so that's an issue the reason
下降，所以这是一个问题，原因
why you don't see anything here is
为什么你在这里什么都看不到
because all of this compiling usually
因为所有这些通常都在编译
happens in the first couple minutes but
发生在最初的几分钟
we run our services for at least a day
我们至少要运行一天的服务
or a couple days right later in the game
或游戏稍后的几天
you really have compilations you do
你真的有汇编
sometimes but for us it's not a big
有时候，但对我们来说，这并不大
issue and we I mean it like Twitter is
问题，我们的意思是像Twitter这样
the perfect you know breeding ground to
您知道的完美的温床
try this compiler because pretty much
试试这个编译器，因为几乎
everything that Twitter does except the
Twitter所做的一切，除了
database in the background is stateless
后台数据库是无状态的
right you gotta treat requests you load
对，您必须处理您加载的请求
it up and return it there's nothing just
把它放回原处
safe there some state so everything
安全一些状态，所以一切
happens in the young gen and so whatever
发生在年轻一代中
if you if you allocate a little bit and
如果你分配一点
then you have to do a collection yeah
那你必须做个收藏耶
well do it so for us it was never an
好吧，对我们来说从来没有
issue but yeah it's something to think
问题，是的，这是值得思考的
about yeah
关于耶
any more questions
还有更多问题
all right thank you
好哒。谢谢你们
[Applause]
[掌声]